# **Emilio Hoffmann Corpus**

1876 N. Forest Hill Pl., Danville, CA

emiliocorpus@gmail.com

Cell: 925-708-0062

## **Professional Summary**

Full-stack web developer with expertise in **Ruby on Rails** and **Object Oriented Javascript**. Efficient problem solver, excellent collaborator and easily adaptable. Inspired to expand current programming capacities. Previous emergency room scribe with over two years experience in electronic medical records.

## **Qualifications**

- Ruby On Rails
- HTML/CSS
- Relational Databases
- Github
- Frontend/Backend Design
- Heroku Deployment
- Experienced Peer Programmer

- Javascript
- Jquery
- React.js
- Git Workflow
- Test Driven Development
- Engineering Empathy
- MVC Frameworks

## **Professional Experience**

### Dev Bootcamp Coding School, San Francisco, CA, 2015

Dev Bootcamp is an immersive web development course that provides aspiring developers the skills to become life-long learners, team players, with a main focus in object oriented Javascript and Ruby on Rails

#### Teaching Assistant, 2015

- Refactoring and code reviews
- Mentor and guide students towards implementing best-practices
- Experience new mechanisms and strategies for solving certain problems

## John Muir Medical Emergency Room, Walnut Creek, CA, 2012–2015

#### **Emergency Room Medical Scribe, 2012–2015**

- Create and manage physician chart templates
- Collaborate with physicians and other healthcare professionals to maintain an efficient workflow
- Compile, write and edit patient histories, physical exams, medical decision making
- Expert in chart workflow, HIPPA, hospital guidelines and regulations

#### University of California-Irvine, 2008-2012

#### Research Lab Assistant, Dr. Michael R. Rose, 2011

- Maintain lab setting and materials
- Dividing and organizing test specimens by gender

### **Education & Certifications**

#### Bachelor of Science, Biology, University of California–Irvine, Irvine, CA 2012

Microbiology, Physiology, Cellular biology, Biochemistry, Organic chemistry, physics

#### 19-Week Web Development, Dev Bootcamp, 2015

- Ruby / Ruby on Rails
- Javascript (Vanilla, Jquery, React.js)
- Engineering Empathy
- Peer programming
- Model View Controller Framework
- Objected Oriented Programming